Guide to the Stanford University Medical Experimental Computer Resource (SUMEX) Records SC1248
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- SUMEX Computer Tapes
  - Archive 204 (copied), 1982 Dec 23; 44.4 (Box 44, Item 4)
  - Archive 206 (copied), 1982 Dec 23; 44.5 (Box 44, Item 5)
  - Archive 208 (copied), 1982 Dec 23; 44.6 (Box 44, Item 6)
  - Archive 210 (copied), 1982 Dec 23; 44.7 (Box 44, Item 7)
  - Archive 212 (copied), 1982 Dec 23; 44.8 (Box 44, Item 8)
  - Archive 214, 1982 Dec 23; 44.9 (Box 44, Item 9)
  - Archive 216 (copied), 1982 Dec 23; 44.10 (Box 44, Item 10)
  - Archive 218 (copied), 1982 Dec 23; 45.1 (Box 45, Item 1)
  - Archive 220 (copied), 1982 Dec 23; 45.2 (Box 45, Item 2)
  - Archive 222 (copied), 1982 Dec 23; 45.3 (Box 45, Item 3)
  - Archive 224 (copied), 1982 Dec 23; 45.4 (Box 45, Item 4)
  - Archive 226 (copied), 1982 Dec 23; 45.5 (Box 45, Item 5)
  - Archive 228 (copied), 1982 Dec 23; 45.6 (Box 45, Item 6)
  - Archive 230 (copied), 1982 Dec 23; 45.7 (Box 45, Item 7)
  - Blue 4 3-1, 45.8 (Box 45, Item 8)
  - Blue 4 3-2; Tape 2 of 2 by WS, 1989 Mar 13; 45.9 (Box 45, Item 9)
  - [Blue 4 3-4], 1989 Mar 21; 45.10 (Box 45, Item 10)
  - Blue 4 3-5, 46.1 (Box 46, Item 1)
  - Blue 4 3-7, 46.2 (Box 46, Item 2)
  - Blue 4 3-8, 1989 Apr 17; 46.3 (Box 46, Item 3)
  - Blue 4 3-9, 1989 Apr 24; 46.4 (Box 46, Item 4)
  - [Blue 4 3-10], 1989 May 15; 46.5 (Box 46, Item 5)
  - Blue 4 3-11, 1989 May 21; 46.6 (Box 46, Item 6)
  - Blue 4 3-12; Tape 1 of 1 by MF, 1989 May 29; 46.7 (Box 46, Item 7)
  - Blue 4 3-14, 46.8 (Box 46, Item 8)
  - Blue 4 3-15, 46.9 (Box 46, Item 9)
  - Blue 4 2-26; Tape 7 of 8 by KS; 1st inode: 75947, 1987 Oct 26; 47.1 (Box 47, Item 1)
  - Blue 4 2-27; Tape 8 of 8 by KS; 1st inode: 90287, 1986 Oct 26; 47.2 (Box 47, Item 2)
  - Blue 4 2-28; Tape 1 of 4 by KS, 1986 Oct 26; 47.3 (Box 47, Item 3)
  - Blue 4 2-29; Tape 2 of 4 by KS; 1st inode: 26742, 1986 Oct 26; 47.4 (Box 47, Item 4)
  - Blue 4 2-30; Tape 3 of 4 by KS; 1st inode: 55303, 1986 Oct 26; 47.5 (Box 47, Item 5)
  - Blue 4 2-31; Tape 4 of 4 by KS; 1st inode: 82010, 1986 Oct 26; 47.6 (Box 47, Item 6)
  - Blue 4 2-32; Tape 1 of 1 by Burgess, 1983 Aug 15; 47.7 (Box 47, Item 7)
  - Blue 4 2-34, 47.8 (Box 47, Item 8)
  - Blue 4 2-35; Software Distribution 9 Track Cusp Tape; Tape Serial # OCT356, 1975 Oct; 47.9 (Box 47, Item 9)
  - 1-1; Archive A1200 by CS, 1987 May; 48.1 (Box 48, Item 1)
  - 1-2; A1202, 48.2 (Box 48, Item 2)
  - 1-3, 48.3 (Box 48, Item 3)
  - 1-4, 48.4 (Box 48, Item 4)
  - 1-5; Archive A1208 by CS, 1987 Jul 12; 48.5 (Box 48, Item 5)
  - 1-27, 48.6 (Box 48, Item 6)
  - 1-28, 48.7 (Box 48, Item 7)
  - 1-29, 48.8 (Box 48, Item 8)
  - 1-30, 48.9 (Box 48, Item 9)
  - 1-33, 48.10 (Box 48, Item 10)
  - 1-34, 49.1 (Box 49, Item 1)
  - 1-35, 49.2 (Box 49, Item 2)
  - 1-36, 49.3 (Box 49, Item 3)
  - 1-38, 49.4 (Box 49, Item 4)
  - 1-39, 49.5 (Box 49, Item 5)
  - 1-40, 49.6 (Box 49, Item 6)
  - 1-41, 49.7 (Box 49, Item 7)
  - 1-42, 49.8 (Box 49, Item 8)
  - 1-43, 49.9 (Box 49, Item 9)
  - Unlabeled, 1990 Dec 9; 49.10 (Box 49, Item 10)
  - 3-8, 50.1 (Box 50, Item 1)
  - 3-11; Tape 1 of 2 by VH, 1991 Apr 28; 50.2 (Box 50, Item 2)
  - 3 1 Dq, 50.3 (Box 50, Item 3)
  - 3 7 Dg, 50.4 (Box 50, Item 4)
  - Blue 5 4 Flat; Mainsail (TM) Mtdump Source Tape; 1600 BPI, 1979 Jul 31; 50.5 (Box 50, Item 5)
  - Blue 5 4 Flat; Mainsail (TM); RSX11M PIP Tape; Hardware Floating Point; 800 BPI, 1979 Jul 30; 50.6 (Box 50, Item 6)
  - Blue 5 4 Flat; Move #2, 50.7 (Box 50, Item 7)
  - Blue 5 4 Flat; Move #3, 50.8 (Box 50, Item 8)
  - Blue 5 4 Flat; Move #4, 50.9 (Box 50, Item 9)
  - Blue 5 4 Flat; Move # 5, 51.1 (Box 51, Item 1)
  - UA 2065 by VH, 1990 Oct 14; 51.2 (Box 51, Item 2)
  - Blue 5 2-33; UA 2066, 51.3 (Box 51, Item 3)
  - Blue 5 2-34; UA 2067, 51.4 (Box 51, Item 4)
  - Blue 5 3-5, 1989 May 1; 51.5 (Box 51, Item 5)
  - [Blue 5 3-11], 51.6 (Box 51, Item 6)
  - Blue 5 3-12, 51.7 (Box 51, Item 7)
  - Blue 5 3-13, 1989 Sept 24; 51.8 (Box 51, Item 8)
  - Blue 5 3-15, 1989 Oct 8; 51.9 (Box 51, Item 9)
  - Blue 5 4 Flat, 52.1 (Box 52, Item 1)
  - Blue 5 3-16, 1989 Oct 22; 52.2 (Box 52, Item 2)
  - Blue 5 3-17, 52.3 (Box 52, Item 3)
  - Blue 5 3-19, 52.4 (Box 52, Item 4)
  - Blue 5 3-23, 52.5 (Box 52, Item 5)
  - Blue 5 3-24, 52.6 (Box 52, Item 6)
  - Unlabeled, 52.7 (Box 52, Item 7)
  - Unlabeled, 52.8 (Box 52, Item 8)
  - Unlabeled, 52.9 (Box 52, Item 9)
  - 2-5, 1987 Sept 2; 53.1 (Box 53, Item 1)
  - 2-7, 53.2 (Box 53, Item 2)
  - 2-8; Tape 1 of 1 by WS, 1988 Jul 24; 53.3 (Box 53, Item 3)
  - 2-9, 53.4 (Box 53, Item 4)
  - 2-10; Tape 2 of 5 by WS; 1st inode: 16636, 1988 Jul 24; 53.5 (Box 53, Item 5)
  - 2-11; Tape 3 of 5 by WS; 1st inode: 26950, 1988 Jul 24; 53.6 (Box 53, Item 6)
  - 2-12, 53.7 (Box 53, Item 7)
  - 2-13; Tape 5 of 5 by WS; 1st inode: 51225, 1988 Jul 24; 53.8 (Box 53, Item 8)
  - 2-14, 53.9 (Box 53, Item 9)
  - 2-15; Tape 2 of 4 by WS; 1st inode: 8652, 1988 Jul 24; 53.10 (Box 53, Item 10)
  - 2-16, 54.1 (Box 54, Item 1)
  - 2-17, 54.2 (Box 54, Item 2)
  - 2-18, 1988 Jun 25; 54.3 (Box 54, Item 3)
  - 2-19, 1988 Jun 25; 54.4 (Box 54, Item 4)
  - 2-21, 54.5 (Box 54, Item 5)
  - 2-22, 54.6 (Box 54, Item 6)
  - 2-23; Tape 1 by DK, 1988 Jan 24; 54.7 (Box 54, Item 7)
  - 2-24, 54.8 (Box 54, Item 8)
  - 6-1, 54.9 (Box 54, Item 9)
  - 6-2, 54.10 (Box 54, Item 10)
  - 6-3; Tape 1 of 1 by VH, 1991 May 19; 55.1 (Box 55, Item 1)
  - 6-6; Tape 1 of 6 by VH, 1991 May 19; 55.2 (Box 55, Item 2)
  - 6-7; Tape 2 of 6 by VH; 1st inode: 67744, 1991 May 19; 55.3 (Box 55, Item 3)
  - 3-47; Archive 293; Tape 1 of 1, 55.4 (Box 55, Item 4)
  - 3-48; Archive 295; Tape 1 of 1, 55.5 (Box 55, Item 5)
  - 3-49; Archive 297; 1600 BPI, 1977 Sept; 55.6 (Box 55, Item 6)
  - 3-50; Archive 299; 1600 BPI, 1977 Sept 19; 55.7 (Box 55, Item 7)
  - 4-1; Archive 301; Time: 17:30; 1600 BPI, 1977 Oct 4; 55.8 (Box 55, Item 8)
  - 4-2; Archive 303; Tape 1 of 1, 1977 Oct 16; 55.9 (Box 55, Item 9)
  - 4-3; Archive 305; Tape 1 of 1, 1977 Oct 27; 55.10 (Box 55, Item 10)
  - 4-4; Archive 307; Time: 1500, 56.1 (Box 56, Item 1)
  - 4-5; Archive 309; Tape 1 of 1, 56.2 (Box 56, Item 2)
  - 4-6; Archive 311; Time: 1500, 56.3 (Box 56, Item 3)
  - 4-7; Archive 313, 1977 Nov 26; 56.4 (Box 56, Item 4)
  - 4-8; Archive 315, 56.5 (Box 56, Item 5)
  - 4-9; Archive 317, 1977 Dec 11; 56.6 (Box 56, Item 6)
  - 4-10; Archive 319; Tape 1 of 1, 1977 Dec 18; 56.7 (Box 56, Item 7)
  - 4-11; Archive 321; Time: 2300, 56.8 (Box 56, Item 8)
  - 4-12; Archive 323; Tape 1 of 1, 1978 Jan 6; 56.9 (Box 56, Item 9)
  - 4-13; Archive 325, 1978 Jan; 57.1 (Box 57, Item 1)
  - 4-14; Archive 327, 1978 Jan 27; 57.2 (Box 57, Item 2)
  - 4-15; Archive 329, 57.3 (Box 57, Item 3)
  - 4-16; Archive 331, 57.4 (Box 57, Item 4)
  - 4-17; Archive 333; Tape 1 of 1, 1978 Feb 21; 57.5 (Box 57, Item 5)
- SUMEX Data printouts
  - Book 4; Archive Listing (even); Tape 302-400, 1977 Oct 4-1978 Nov 13 (Box 60)
  - Printouts (Box 61)
  - Book 5; Archive Listing (odd); Tapes 401-499, 1979 Nov 22-1979 Dec 12 (Box 62)
  - Book 2; Archive Listing (even); Tapes 102-200, 1976 Apr 5-1976 Dec 22 (Box 63)
  - Printouts, 1977 (Box 64)